Guide to the Cornell University Basketball Films,1957-1985.
Cornell University basketball films,1957-1985.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University basketball films, 1957-1985.
40-3-3120
Cornell University.Dept. of Athletics and Physical Education.
21 cubic ft.
Movie Film
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Films, video cassettes, and video reels of Cornell basketball games. Includes games with Air Force, Bowling Green, Broome Tech, Brown, Bucknell, Canisius, Carlton, Cleveland State, Clemson, Colgate, Columbia, Dartmouth, Fordham, Harvard, Hofstra, Manhattanville, Niagara, the University of Northern Iowa, Northeastern, Northwestern, Notre Dame, Oklahoma, the University of Pennsylvania, Portugal, Princeton, Rensselaer Polytech, Robert Morris, Rochester, St. Bonaventure, St. Joseph's, Syracuse, Utica, Vermont, and Yale. Includes films of basketball tournaments.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Films, video cassettes, and video reels of Cornell basketball games. Includes games with Air Force, Bowling Green, Broome Tech, Brown, Bucknell, Canisius, Carlton, Cleveland State, Clemson, Colgate, Columbia, Dartmouth, Fordham, Harvard, Hofstra, Manhattanville, Niagara, the University of Northern Iowa, Northeastern, Northwestern, Notre Dame, Oklahoma, the University of Pennsylvania, Portugal, Princeton, Rensselaer Polytech, Robert Morris, Rochester, St. Bonaventure, St. Joseph's, Syracuse, Utica, Vermont, and Yale. Includes films of basketball tournaments.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Bowling Green State University--Basketball.; Broome Community College--Basketball.; Brown University--Basketball.; Bucknell University--Basketball.; Canisius College--Basketball.; Carlton College--Basketball.; Clemson University--Basketball.; Cleveland State University--Basketball.; Colgate University--Basketball.; Columbia University--Basketball.; Cornell University--Athletics.; Cornell University--Basketball.; Dartmouth College--Basketball.; Fordham University--Basketball.; Harvard University--Basketball.; Hofstra University--Basketball.; Manhattanville College--Basketball.; Niagara University--Basketball.; Northeastern University--Basketball.; Northwestern University--Basketball.; Princeton University--Basketball.; Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute--Basketball.; Robert Morris College (Ill.)--Basketball.; St. Bonaventure University--Basketball.; Syracuse University--Basketball.; United States Air Force Academy--Basketball.; University of Northern Iowa--Basketball.; University of Notre Dame--Basketball.; University of Oklahoma--Basketball.; University of Pennsylvania--Basketball.; University of Rochester--Basketball.; University of Vermont--Basketball.; Utica College--Basketball.; Yale University--Basketball.
Subjects:
Basketball.; Basketball--Tournaments--United States.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Link to the printed finding aid. PDF file
- DVDs Available of the following. See above link for all films.
  - Cornell vs. Dartmouth, pt. 1, 1959 (Box 5, Reel #85), 1959; 782
  - Cornell vs. Dartmouth, pt. 2, 1959 (Box 5, Reel #86), 1959; 782
  - Cornell vs. Dartmouth, pt. 3, 1959 (Box 5, Reel #87), 1959; 782
  - Cornell vs. Pennsylvania, pt. 1, 2/27/1977 (Box 19, Reel #48), February 27, 1977; 135
  - Cornell vs. Pennsylvania, pt. 2, 2/27/1977 (Box 19, Reel #49), February 27, 1977; 135
  - Cornell vs. Pennsylvania, pt. 1, 3/4/1978 (Box 19, Reel #51), March 4, 1978; 130
  - Cornell vs. Pennsylvania, pt. 1, 3/4/1978 (Box 19, Reel #52), March 4, 1978; 130
    Includes narration, (by coach?)
  - Cornell vs. Pennsylvania, pt. 1, 2/23/1979 (Box 19, Reel #55), February 23, 1979; 127
  - Cornell vs. Pennsylvania, 3/6/1981 (Box 16, Video Cassette #35), March 6, 1981; 129
  - Cornell vs. Pennsylvania, 3/5/1982 (Box 16, Video Cassette #36), March 5, 1982; 128